{
  "topics": [
    {
      "name": "topic1",
      "level1": [
        {
          "id": "question1",
          "question": "Question 1",
          "answer": "Answer of question 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "question1-2",
          "question": "Question 1-2",
          "answer": "Answer of question 1-2"
        },
        {
          "id": "question1-3",
          "question": "Question 1-3",
          "answer": "Answer of question 1-3"
        }
      ],
      "level2": [
        {
          "id": "question2",
          "question": "Question 2",
          "answer": "Answer of question 2"
        }
      ],
      "level3": [
        {
          "id": "question3",
          "question": "Question 3",
          "answer": "Answer of question 3"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "topic2",
      "level1": [
        {
          "id": "question4",
          "question": "Question 4",
          "answer": "Answer of question 4"
        }
      ],
      "level2": [
        {
          "id": "question5",
          "question": "Question 5",
          "answer": "Answer of question 5"
        }
      ],
      "level3": [
        {
          "id": "question6",
          "question": "Question 6",
          "answer": "Answer of question 6"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "topic3",
      "level1": [
        {
          "id": "question7",
          "question": "Question 7",
          "answer": "Answer of question 7"
        }
      ],
      "level2": [
        {
          "id": "question8",
          "question": "Question 8",
          "answer": "Answer of question 8"
        }
      ],
      "level3": [
        {
          "id": "question9",
          "question": "Question 9",
          "answer": "Answer of question 9"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
